<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on david / dev journal</title><link>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on david / dev journal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 12:45:53 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Towards the First Demo</title><link>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/first-demo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 12:45:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/first-demo/</guid><description>It has been an active week regarding the development of the game! All teams have been working hard in order to have ready for yesterday, April 16th, an amazing first demo of what will be their game, showing the core concepts and mechanics of them. Of course, time has been extremely limited and the demos were relatively basic, but I was amazed of the work many teams have done in such little time.</description></item><item><title>First Steps and Logo Design</title><link>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/first-steps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:54:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/first-steps/</guid><description>One of the hardest parts in a project is to start with it. Specially if one is part of a group, which is chosen randomly, and which is asked to produce a game (or an extensive enough demo) in over two months. Well, this is where I was.
Brainstorming Brainstorming is a method design teams use to generate ideas to solve clearly defined design problems. In controlled conditions and a free-thinking environment, teams approach a problem by such means as “How Might We” questions.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:40:58 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dvcarrillo.com/DH2650-blog/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello world! This is the first entry of my game dev journal, a blog that I will regularly update to keep track of my progress during the development of our project for the subject DH2650 Computer Game Design at KTH Royal Institute of Technology.
What will you find here? I will focus on reflecting on my individual contributions, organization of the team and general updates of our project. The content will range from topics like programming to illustration, according to my work and needs of the team.</description></item></channel></rss>